var questionAnswers = [
    {
    question: "In the year 1900 in the U.S. what were the most popular first names given to boy and girl babies?",
    correctAnswer: "C. John and Mary",
    answers: {
        answerA: "A. William and Elizabeth",
        answerB: "B. Joseph and Catherine",
        answerC: "C. John and Mary",
        answerD: "D. George and Anne"
        }
    },
    {
    question: "When did the Liberty Bell get its name?",
    correctAnswer: "C. in the 19th century, when it became a symbol of the abolition of slavery",
    answers: {
        answerA: "A. when it was made, in 1701",
        answerB: "B. when it rang on July 4, 1776",
        answerC: "C. in the 19th century, when it became a symbol of the abolition of slavery",
        answerD: "D. none of the above"
        }
    },
    {
        question: "In the Roy Rogers -Dale Evans Museum, you will find Roy and Dales stuffed horses. Roy's horse was named Trigger, which was Dales horse?",
        correctAnswer: "A. Buttermilk",
        answers: {
            answerA: "A. Buttermilk",
            answerB: "B. Daisy",
            answerC: "C. Scout",
            answerD: "D. Tulip"
        }
    },
    {
    question: "The Daniel Boon museum at the home where he died can best be described how?",
    correctAnswer: "C. a four-story Georgian-style home in Missouri",
    answers: {
        answerA: "A. a log cabin in Kentucky",
        answerB: "B. a two-story clapboard house in Tennessee",
        answerC: "C. a four-story Georgian-style home in Missouri",
        answerD: "D. a three story brick house in Arkansas"
        }
    },
    {
    question: "Which of the following items was owned by the fewest U.S. homes in 1990?",
    correctAnswer: "B. CD player",
    answers: {
        answerA: "A. home computer",
        answerB: "B. CD player",
        answerC: "C. cordless phone",
        answerD: "D. dishwasher"
        }
    },
    {
    question: "Who holds the record for the most victories in a row on the professional golf tour?",
    correctAnswer: "C. Byron Nelson",
    answers: {
        answerA: "A. Jack Nicklaus",
        answerB: "B. Arnold Palmer",
        answerC: "C. Byron Nelson",
        answerD: "D. Ben Hogan"
        }
    },
    {
    question: "Who is third behind Hank Aaron and Babe Ruth in major league career home runs?",
    correctAnswer: "C. Willie Mays",
    answers: {
        answerA: "A. Reggie Jackson",
        answerB: "B. Harmon Killebrew",
        answerC: "C. Willie Mays",
        answerD: "D. Frank Robinson"
        }
    },
    {
    question: "In 1990, in what percentage of U.S. married couples did the wife earn more money than the husband?",
    correctAnswer: "B. 18%",
    answers: {
        answerA: "A. 8%",
        answerB: "B. 18%",
        answerC: "C. 38%",
        answerD: "D. 58%"
        }
    },
    {
    question: "During the 1980s for six consecutive years what breed of dog was the most popular in the U.S.?",
    correctAnswer: "A. cocker spaniel",
    answers: {
        answerA: "A. cocker spaniel",
        answerB: "B. German shepherd",
        answerC: "C. Labrador retriever",
        answerD: "D. poodle"
        }
    },
    {
    question: "In 1985, five percent of U.S. households had telephone answering machines. By 1990 what percentage of homes had answering machines?",
    correctAnswer: "C. 31%",
    answers: {
        answerA: "A. 10%",
        answerB: "B. 11%",
        answerC: "C. 31%",
        answerD: "D. 51%"
        }
    },
    {
    question: "The first black American pictured on a U.S. postage stamp was who?",
    correctAnswer: "D. Joe Louis",
    answers: {
        answerA: "A. Frederick Douglass",
        answerB: "B. Booker T. Washington",
        answerC: "C. Louis Armstrong",
        answerD: "D. Joe Louis"
        }
    },
    {
    question: "What did the 'D' in 'D-Day' stand for?",
    correctAnswer: "B. day",
    answers: {
        answerA: "A. doom",
        answerB: "B. day",
        answerC: "C. Dwight (Eisenhower)",
        answerD: "D. Dunkirk"
        }
    },
    {
    question: "The Brownie Box Camera introduced by Eastman Kodak in 1900 had a retail price of what?",
    correctAnswer: "A. $1",
    answers: {
        answerA: "A. $1",
        answerB: "B. $5",
        answerC: "C. $10",
        answerD: "D. $20"
        }
    },
    {
    question: "Which of these characters turned 40 years old in 1990?",
    correctAnswer: "A. Charlie Brown",
    answers: {
        answerA: "A. Charlie Brown",
        answerB: "B. Bugs Bunny",
        answerC: "C. Mickey Mouse",
        answerD: "D. Fred Flintstone"
        }
    },
    {
    question: "The Philadelphia mint started putting a 'P' mint mark on quarters when?",
    correctAnswer: "B. 1980",
    answers: {
        answerA: "A. 1960",
        answerB: "B. 1980",
        answerC: "C. 1990",
        answerD: "D. never"
        }
    },
    {
    question: "Before becoming George Bush's Secretary of Defense, what was Dick Cheney's position?",
    correctAnswer: "A. congressman from Wyoming",
    answers: {
        answerA: "A. congressman from Wyoming",
        answerB: "B. governor of New Hampshire",
        answerC: "C. secretary of defense under Ronald Reagan",
        answerD: "D. business owner"
        }
    },
    {
        question: "When Mt. St. Helens erupted on May 18, 1980, how many people were killed?",
        correctAnswer: "B. 57",
        answers: {
            answerA: "A. 1",
            answerB: "B. 57",
            answerC: "C. 571",
            answerD: "D. 5714"
        }
    },
    {
        question: "In J. Edgar Hoover, what did the J stand for?",
        correctAnswer: "B. John",
        answers: {
            answerA: "A. James",
            answerB: "B. John",
            answerC: "C. Jonathan",
            answerD: "D. Joseph"
        }
    },
    {
        question: "Florence Nightingale became known as 'the Lady With the Lamp' during which war?",
        correctAnswer: "B. Crimean War",
        answers: {
            answerA: "A. American Civil War",
            answerB: "B. Crimean War",
            answerC: "C. World War I",
            answerD: "D. Korean War"
        }
    },
    {
        question: "What year was it that the Census Bureau first reported that a majority of new mothers were remaining in the new job market?",
        correctAnswer: "D. 1988",
        answers: {
            answerA: "A. 1958",
            answerB: "B. 1968",
            answerC: "C. 1978",
            answerD: "D. 1988"
        }
    },
]